# Luciano Nicolás Díaz

Buenos Aires Province, Argentina



luchodiaz1995@gmail.com



+541159102957



linkedin.com/in/lucianonicolasdiaz



https://diazluciano.github.io/portfolio/

# **Summary**

I am a developer with a Full Stack profile. My main stack is .NET for the Backend development and Angular for Frontend development. I've worked in the development and maintenance about websites, web applications SPA, REST APIs and SQL Server databases. Regarding the work environment, I have developed my tasks in an agile environment following the SCRUM methodology using the Jira tool. I have also worked in a environment where the common language to communicate was English. My goal is to improve my stack in an environment that allows me to grow as a professional developer.

## **Experience**



## Full Stack Engineer

#### Banco Supervielle

Mar 2022 - Jun 2023 (1 year 4 months)

- I have continued with developments from my previous experience at IUDU becasue this company belonged to Supervielle Bank until I moved on to another type of project within the Bank.
- SPA application development using Angular 14 and Angular Material.
- Microservice development using the BFF architecture pattern.
- Development of new functionalities for a REST Api based on .Net Core 3.1.
- Project versioning using Git and GitLab as repository.
- Deployments of new versions using CI/CD with pipes configured in GitLab.
- Teamwork following Scrum agile methodology using Jira tool.
- Reason for resignation: Travel abroad



# Full Stack Engineer

#### IUDÚ

Mar 2022 - Aug 2022 (6 months)

- SPA application development using Angular 14.
- Interface design development using external library Fuse Template.
- Layout using SCSS.
- Testing development using Karma/Jasmine.
- Synchronization of new changes and enhancements using Git and AzureDevOps as repository.
- Teamwork following Scrum agile methodology using Jira tool.
- Reason for Resignation: The company went bankrupt but it belonged to Banco Supervielle, so continue with the relationship with the Bank and its projects.



## Full Stack Engineer

#### Globant

May 2021 - Mar 2022 (11 months)

- Maintenance and Support to client's teams on an advertising space sales platform.
- Testing development using Karma/Jasmine and NUnit.

- New developments using .Net Core 3.1, C#, JQuery and JavaScript.
- Teamwork following Scrum agile methodology using Jira tool.
- Project versioning using Git and AzureDevOps as repository.
- -Reason for Resignation: I was looking for a salary jump, greater participation in projects and a development space using Angular.

# Full Stack Engineer

Time Solution Software

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021 (1 year 3 months)

- Development and maintenance of Web Applications (Web Forms, Web Api, ASP.NET and .NET Framework).
- Development and maintenance of Web Desktops (Windows Forms).
- Database management and development (MS SQL Server, T-SQL).
- Team communication through Discord and Trello.
- Project versioning using Git and GitHub as repository.
- Reason for Resignation: I was looking for a job in more advanced technologies and a larger team that uses the SCRUM methodology.

### **Education**

# **\*∪TN Universidad Tecnológica Nacional**

University Technician in Computer Systems, Computer Technology/Computer Systems Technology

Mar 2020 - Mar 2021

### **\*∪TN Universidad Tecnológica Nacional**

University Technician in Programming, Computer Programming Mar 2018 - Mar 2020

### **Skills**

Firebase • TypeScript • scss • .NET Core • Angular • Microsoft SQL Server • REST APIs • ASP.NET • C# • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)